downnotifier.com 2019-04-11

# DownNotifier.com - Privacy policy

This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their 'Personally Identifiable Information' (PII) is being used online. PII is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.

## What personal information do we collect from the people that visit downnotifier.com?

When using our service, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address, phone number or other details to help you with your experience.

## When do we collect information?

We collect information from you when you register on our site or enter information on our site.

## How do we use your information?

We may use the information we collect from for providing the service, sending our newsletter or use certain other site features.

## How do we protect your information?

Our website is scanned on a regular basis for security holes and known vulnerabilities in order to make your visit to our site as safe as possible.

Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology. 

All transactions are processed through a gateway provider and are not stored or processed on our servers.

## Do we use cookies?

Yes. Cookies are used to remember your login. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may use cookies to track marketing campaigns. 

## Third-party disclosure

We do not sell or trade your Personally Identifiable Information to outside parties.

We may exchange your Personally Identifiable Information to provide the DownNotifier.com service, for example the phone number to an SMS carrier.
